# **Mahmoud Alsayed Alboraye**

# Front end Web Developer

# **About Me**

Front End developer building websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript. React.js + Redux I specialized in JavaScript and have some experience working with PHP, MySQL, Magento 2, Laravel Framework, familiar with Jira, G Suite, I can use my skills, learning along the way,I am a self-motivated person have a great passion for programming

what I'm doing now is:

Practicing on creating web apps using React.js + Redux, learning PWA

# **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React.js + Redux
- npm
- git
- MVC

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

Mobile : +201062330082

Email : mahmoudalsayied@gmail.com Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-alsayied Github : github.com/mahmoud-sayed Address : 37 - 9 street shubra new street

Qalyubia

## **EDUCATION**

**High Institute Four Computer & Information System** 

studying time | 09 . 2012 - 09 . 2016

#### **Material Studied**

- information technology
- marketing
- finance

#### **COURSES**

- - Udemy Complete JavaScript Course
- Udemy Modern React with Redux
- - Udemy course in Data Structure and Algorithm, OOP

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Magento Developer**

at Best Response Media | 7. 2019 - 11 . 2020

Best Response Media is an Enterprise Magento solution partner and ( Adobe Gold partner) Working mainly with Magento 2.x and 1.9 (opensource, Commerce, Cloud).

My responsibilities:

- Support my team in Fixing some issues.
- I have participated in Creating custom modules.
- participated in admin configuration

#### php-Laravel Developer

SpectraApps | 12.2018 - 03.2019

SpectraApps, is an development company creating new Web Apps and Mobile Apps, support and maintaining existing apps.

My responsibilities:

- creating new projects.

#### **Digital Signage solutions manager**

Marketising-Egypt | 09 . 2017 - 03 . 2018

developing and managing clients' digital strategy to improve their web presence and achieve their digital marketing goals with our company, solve digital problems inside digital locations.